[singing]
[heartbeat sound]
[upbeat music]
As you came into the window was the sound
of a crescendo.
He came into your apartment. He left the
bloodstains on the carpet.
She ran under the table. You could see
she was unable.
So she ran into the bedroom. She was
struck down, it was her doom.
Annie, are you okay? So Annie, are you
okay?
Are you okay, Annie? Annie, are you okay?
So Annie, are you okay?
Will you tell us that you're okay?
There's a sign in the window that he
struck you a crescendo, Annie.
He came into your apartment, left the
bloodstains on the carpet.
Then you ran into the bedroom. You were
struck down.
It was your doom. Annie, are you okay? So
Annie, are you okay?
Are you okay, Annie? Annie, are you okay?
So Annie, are you okay?
Are you okay, Annie? You've been hit by.
You've been hit by a smooth criminal.
[upbeat music] Ow!
See they came into the outway. It was
Sunday, what a black day.
Murder members of the station. Sounding
heartbeats, intimidations.
Annie, are you okay? So Annie, are you
okay?
Are you okay, Annie? Annie, are you okay?
So Annie, are you okay?
Annie, are you okay? Are you okay, Annie?
Annie, are you okay?
So Annie, are you okay? Are you okay,
Annie?
Annie, are you okay? So Annie, are you
okay?
Are you okay, Annie? Annie, are you okay?
Will you tell us that you're
okay? There's a sign in the window that
he struck you a crescendo, Annie.
He came into your apartment, left the
bloodstains on the carpet.
Then you ran into the bedroom. You were
struck down.
It was your doom. Annie, are you okay? So
Annie, are you okay?
Are you okay, Annie? You've been hit by.
You've been struck by a smooth criminal.
[upbeat music]
Ow! I want everybody to stay there
right now.
[singing] [upbeat music] Annie, are you
okay?
I know you are. Will you tell us
that you're okay? I know you are. There's
a sign in the window.
I know you are. That he struck you a
crescendo, Annie.
I know you are. He came into your
apartment.
I know you are. Left the bloodstains on
the carpet.
I know you are. Then you ran into the
bedroom.
You are. You were struck down. It was
your doom, Annie.
Annie, are you okay? Will you tell us
that you're okay?
That you are, baby. There's a sign in the
window.
That you are, baby. That he struck
you a crescendo, Annie. He came into your
apartment.
That you are. Left the bloodstains on the
carpet.
Hey. Then you ran into the bedroom. Hey.
You were struck down.
That you are. It was your doom. Ow!
[upbeat music]
Ow! [upbeat music] Chugga-chugga,
chugga-chugga.
Ow! [upbeat music]